Ying-Chun Lin Jean

Email: <u>ljn101106@gmail.com</u> Personal Website: <u>ycjeanlin.github.io</u>

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in data mining, recommender systems and machine learning. I am fascinated by how to find the valuable knowledge from the abundance of data and further improve human life. Today, the information around us is too much to consume. Motivated by the information explosion, I recently focus on how to filter the information around us and help us to make better choices. I have been studying about real-time recommender system to solve the filtering problem recently.

EDUCATION

Jan 2014 – July 2016	National Cheng Kung University, Taiwan Master of Science in Computer Science and Information Engineering
Sep 2009 – June 2013	National Cheng Kung University, Taiwan Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering
Aug 2014 – Dec 2012	Auburn University, Alabama, U.S.A. Exchange student in Electrical Engineering

PUBLICATIONS

May 2015	Ying Chun Lin, Cheng-Wei Wu, Vincent S. Tseng, Mining High Utility
	Itemsets in Big Data, In Proceedings of the International Pacific-Asia
	Conference on Knowledge Discovery and Data Mining, pp.649 - 661.
	(DAKDD '15)

WORK EXPERIENCE

WORKE DATE DIGID.	TICE
July 2015 – Aug 2015	Yahoo Taiwan Intern of Software engineering in Search Team
	Worked for a project "Search Nearby" in which the search result is adjusted according to the ephemeral needs and location of users
Aug 2013 – May 2014	NetDB Lab in National Cheng-Kung University, Taiwan Research Assistant
	Studied the topic of how to disseminate messages via mobile P2P network Implemented and maintained the website of PAKDD 2014
Jan 2013 – July 2013	MRI Center in National Cheng-Kung University, Taiwan Software Engineer
	Implemented and maintained the center website

AWARDS

Big Data Analytics for Semiconductor Manufacturing the Award of Excellence in the TSMC Big Data Competition

April 2016 – Present slice, USA Working on a research topic "User Segmenting with Temporal Factor for Targeted Advertising"

July 2014 – Dec 2014 Industrial Technology Research Institute, Taiwan

Research Assistant

Worked on a research topic "An Efficient Algorithm for On-Shelf Sequential

Pattern Mining"

KEY SKILLS

Programming language:

Java, C, C++, Verilog, PHP, R, Python, MATLAB

Languages:

Chinese(Native), English (TOEFLreading:22, listening:22, speaking:17, writing:20; before going to the US)

Last modified: 2016/07/07